Applying for :-

A Job as a Student

PROFILE

Name: Rajwinder Singh

Age: 20 years Status: Student

Address: 34 Davenfield Cr, Brampton, ON

L6P 4M2

This position would enable me to use my strong organizational skills, award-winning educational background, and ability to work well with people. Through all my past experiences, I learnt how to be a good team member and how to deal with any difficult situation with ease.

CONTACT

PHONE:

+1 (647)772-2213

EMAIL:

mexrobi2001@gmail.com

HOBBIES

Social person Reading Interactive formations Technology

Rajwinder Singh

EDUCATION

HIGH SCHOOL - Victoria International School, Mukerian 2017 — 2020

I secured highest GPA in all my grades and I had participated in all competitions such as QUIZ, SPEECH, DEBATE, ARTS etc and won prizes and moreover I had been selected as the captain of house and I had experience to lead a number of people.

Seneca College , Newhnum Campus, Toronto

<u>2021 – Present</u>

Currently I am in my first semester and I am securing good grades in tests and assignments and moreover my programs in computer science are loved by my teacher.

WORK EXPERIENCE

<u>Career Consultant</u>, <u>Storage Warehouse</u> Sept 2020-Dec 2020 , <u>Jan 2021- May 2021</u>

I had worked in an education institution as an assistant Instructor, and I had given workshops to 100 students at one time and I had experience to control and deliver lecture to 40-50 students at one time. Also worked and have experience for working in a storage place, coordinating with other workerswhile being consistent towards my work. Confertable with physical work as well as sitting on a computer screen for entries , logs, data and other works.

SKILLS

- Great communication skills
- Decision making
- Leadership
- Computer and technology
- Adaptability
- Innovative thinking
- Sales minded
- Modesty
- Relationship builders
- Sense of responsibility
- Good observation skills

LANGUAGES:

- Hindi
- Punjabi
- English